Where we're going, we don't need ropes...
The Marks is a comedy film directed by Joseph Lavender.
The daughter of a pro-wrestling legend operates a backyard wrestling organization called, "Mosh
Pitt Wrestling Association" out of her granny's backyard in this irreverent comedy.
Maggie Lightning, played by Laurie Catherine Winkel.
Jack Dixon, played by Joey Thurmond.
Bishop Moneybaggs, played by Jason Louder.
Sam, played by Gunner Willis.
Truck Driver, played by William Tokarsky.
Bobbi Wire, played by Erika Chase.
Mark is a 2025 Indian Kannada-language action thriller film directed and written by Vijay
Kartikeyaa and produced jointly by Sathya Jyothi Films and Kichcha Creations.
The film's ensemble cast include Sudeepa, marking his second collaboration with Vijay following their successful 2024 film Max, along with Naveen Chandra,
Shine Tom Chacko, Vikranth,  Roshni Prakash, Guru Somasundaram, Yogi Babu, Deepshika, Dragon Manju, Gopalkrishna Deshpande and Nishvika Naidu.
Principal photography commenced in early July 2025 and concluded in approximately 110 days, with key
locations including Bengaluru’s Kanakapura Road and several sets across Karnataka.
Post-production—including visual effects, background score, and dubbing—was completed by
mid-November 2025 with the film’s official trailer unveiling on 7 December 2025.
The film had a pan-Indian theatrical release on 25 December
2025 to capitalize on the Christmas season.
It was simultaneously released in Kannada alongside a partially reshot Tamil
version and dubbed versions in Telugu, Malayalam, and Hindi.
The film explores themes of wrestling, pro wrestling, all elite wrestling
(aew), world wrestling entertainment (wwe), hilarious.
The tone is lighthearted.